♪Just wanna say hello♪
♪ فقط أريد أن أقول مرحبًا ♪
♪Hello♪
♪ مرحبا ♪
♪You are so unstoppable♪
♪ أنت لا يمكن إيقافك ♪
=Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2= =Episode 12=
= Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2 = = الحلقة 12 =
You are pretty good at playing innocent.
أنت جيد جدًا في لعب دور بريء.
You are not that bad yourself either.
أنت لست بهذا السوء أيضا.
Let's have a toast for our encounter.
دعونا نتناول نخب لقاءنا.
Why are you so clumsy?
لماذا أنت أخرق جدا؟
Here.
هنا.
Don't panic.
لا تُصب بالذعر.
Put this on.
البس هذا.
This shawl suits you so well.
هذا الشال يناسبك جيدًا.
It was made for you.
تم صنعه من أجلك.
Get in there.
ادخل هناك.
Are you nuts?
هل انت مجنون؟
Save her!
أنقذها!
You deserve it!
تستحقها!
Are you cold?
هل تشعر بالبرد؟
Yun Xiangxiang.
يون شيانغشيانغ.
What did you do?
ما الذي فعلته؟
They started it.
لقد بدأوا ذلك.
I was just returning the favor.
كنت فقط أرد الجميل.
An eye for an eye.
العين بالعين.
You went too far, Yun Xiangxiang.
ذهبت بعيدا جدا ، يون شيانغ شيانغ.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
I'm getting tired of this act.
لقد تعبت من هذا الفعل.
Some unreasonable women.
بعض النساء غير عقلانيات.
I'm leaving.
سأغادر.
You...
أنت...
Yun Xiangxiang.
يون شيانغشيانغ.
You treat our guests like this.
أنت تعامل ضيوفنا مثل هذا.
You bring disgrace on not just me,
أنت تجلب العار ليس فقط لي ،
but also the whole Fu family.
ولكن أيضًا عائلة فو بأكملها.
Save it. Do you think you can threaten me with that?
احفظها.  هل تعتقد أنك يمكن أن تهددني بذلك؟
Xiangxiang didn't bring disgrace on the family.
Xiangxiang لم يجلب العار على الأسرة.
I think she did very well.
اعتقد انها عملت بشكل جيد جدا.
Your previous parties were so boring.
كانت حفلاتك السابقة مملة للغاية.
The reporters couldn't find anything to write about.
لم يتمكن الصحفيون من العثور على أي شيء يكتبون عنه.
But this year, at least you have a wet party.
لكن هذا العام ، على الأقل لديك حفلة رطبة.
Isn't it?
أليس كذلك؟
You mean I should thank her for that?
تقصد أنني يجب أن أشكرها على ذلك؟
Are you still cold?
هل مازلت باردا؟
Your warmth
دفئك
drove all the coldness away.
دفع كل البرودة بعيدا.
I'm tired, darling.
أنا متعب يا عزيزتي.
Can we go back?
هل يمكننا الرجوع؟
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Yeah.
نعم.
Ms. Fu.
السيدة فو.
Why is Sihan so good to her?
لماذا سيهان جيدة لها؟
I told you.
أخبرتك.
She's not as innocent as she looks.
إنها ليست بريئة كما تبدو.
Why are you guys here?
لماذا أنتم هنا يا رفاق؟
Mr. Fu was worried
كان السيد فو قلقا
that you couldn't handle it on your own.
لا يمكنك التعامل معها بنفسك.
So we rushed to the party.
لذلك هرعنا إلى الحفلة.
Only to find out that you managed it beautifully.
فقط لتكتشف أنك تمكنت من إدارتها بشكل جميل.
Chu He.
تشو هي.
Do you still want your annual bonus?
هل مازلت تريد مكافأتك السنوية؟
Don't worry about me.
لا تقلق علي.
Those are merely child's tricks for me.
هذه مجرد حيل للأطفال بالنسبة لي.
I'm way better at that.
أنا أفضل حالًا في ذلك.
So? Was I doing fine today?
لذا؟  هل كنت بخير اليوم؟
Do I get an A plus?
هل أحصل على A plus؟
More or less.
الى حد ما.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
You had a few drops there.
كان لديك بضع قطرات هناك.